Guide to the Cornell University Libraries records of gifts,1894-1971.
Cornell University Libraries records of gifts, 1894-1971.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Libraries records of gifts, 1894-1971.
13-3-986
Cornell University. Libraries. Acquisitions Dept. Gifts, Exchange and Approvals Section.
9 cubic ft.
Volumes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
92 volumes containing information on gifts donated to the Cornell University Libraries.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
92 volumes containing information on gifts donated to the Cornell University Libraries.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Libraries. Acquisitions Dept. Gifts, Exchange and Approvals Section.; Cornell University--Libraries.
Subjects:
Libraries--Gifts, legacies.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Arranged chronologically.
CONTAINER LIST
- Oct. 23 1894- Nov. 6 1899 (Box 1)
- Nov. 14 1899- Oct. 25 1901 (Box 1)
- Oct. 26 1901- Sept. 14 1903 (Box 1)
- Sept. 24 1903- Apr. 29 1905 (Box 1)
- May 1 1905- Nov. 10 1906 (Box 1)
- Nov. 23 1906- Jan. 1908 (Box 1)
- Jan. 16 1908- Jan. 30 1909 (Box 1)
- Feb. 8 1909- Jan. 10 1910 (Box 1)
- Jan. 1 1910- Dec. 28 1910 (Box 1)
- Jan. 3 1911- Feb. 29 1912 (Box 1)
- Mar. 1 1912- Dec. 31 1912 (Box 1)
- Jan. l913-Jan. 1914 (Box 2)
- 1914 (Box 2)
- 1915 (Box 2)
- 1915-1916 (Box 2)
- 1916-1917 (Box 2)
- 1917-1918 (Box 2)
- 1918-1919 (Box 2)
- 1919-1920 (Box 2)
- 1920-1921 (Box 3)
- 1921-1922 (Box 3)
- 1922-1923 (Box 3)
- 1923-1924 (Box 3)
- 1924-1925 (Box 3)
- 1925-1926 (Box 3)
- 1926-1927 (Box 3)
- 1927-1928 (Box 3)
- 1928-1929 (Box 3)
- 1929-1930 (Box 3)
- 1930-1931 (Box 3)
- 1931-1932 (Box 3)
- 1932-1933 A-I (Box 4)
- 1932-1933 J-Z (Box 4)
- 1933-1934 A-I (Box 4)
- 1933-1934 J-Z (Box 4)
- 1934-1935 A-I (Box 4)
- 1934-1935 J-Z (Box 4)
- 1935-1936 A-I (Box 4)
- 1935-1936 J-Z (Box 4)
- 1936-1937 A-I (Box 4)
- 1936-1937 J-Z (Box 4)
- 1937-1938 A-I (Box 4)
- 1937-1938 J-Z (Box 4)
- 1938-1939 A-I (Box 4)
- 1938-1939 J-Z (Box 5)
- 1939-1940 A-I (Box 5)
- 1939-1940 J-Z (Box 5)
- 1940-1941 A-E (Box 5)
- 1940-1941 F-N (Box 5)
- 1940-1941 0-Z (Box 5)
- 1941-1942 A-K (Box 5)
- 1941-1942 L-Z (Box 5)
- 1942-1943 A-H (Box 5)
- 1942-1943 I-Z (Box 5)
- 1943-1944 A-L (Box 6)
- 1943-1944 M-Z (Box 6)
- 1944-1945 A-I (Box 6)
- 1944-1945 J-Z (Box 6)
- 1945-1946 A-I (Box 6)
- 1945-1946 J-Z (Box 6)
- 1946-1947 A-I (Box 6)
- 1946-1947 J-Z (Box 6)
- 1947-1948 A-K (Box 6)
- 1947-1948 L-Z (Box 6)
- 1948-1949 A-I (Box 6)
- 1948-1949 J-Z (Box 6)
- 1949-1950 A-H (Box 6)
- 1949-1950 I-Z (Box 6)
- 1950-1951 A-H (Box 7)
- 1950-1951 I-Z (Box 7)
- 1951-1952 A-I (Box 7)
- 1951-1952 J-Z (Box 7)
- 1952-1953 A-K (Box 7)
- 1952-1953 L-Z (Box 7)
- 1954-1955 A-Z (Box 7)
- 1955-1956 A-Z (Box 7)
- 1953-1954 A-Z (Box 7)
- 7 volumes of gifts, 1956-1963 (Box 8-9)
- 8 volumes of gifts, 1963-1971 (Box 9)